<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Cesar Recio</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Cesar Recio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Data Between Choosing an NFL team &amp;amp; the political stance you take as a fan of that team The two datasets that we are going to be exploring takes into account NFL Fandom. For one of the datasets, it takes into account the race and politcal views of fans of particular NFL teams. The other datasets contain variables that factor into how people choose on what their favorite NFL team will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, Predicting The dataset that we are going to model and test looks into the test score data and income in California Schools in different counties across California. Some of the variables that we will take into account include County, District Average income(in 1,000 USD), average reading score, average math score, and number of computers. A categorical variable (County) is include with 6 groups, a total of 97 observations for Average reading score in schools in a specific county, a total of 97 observations of Average math score in schools in a specific county, and 97 observations of total number of computers in schools in a county.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
